What does it take to prove the impossible?
The Man Who Knew Infinity is a drama, history film directed by Matt Brown.
Growing up poor in Madras, India, Srinivasa Ramanujan Iyengar earns admittance to Cambridge University during
WWI, where he becomes a pioneer in mathematical theories with the guidance of his professor, G.H.
Srinivasa Ramanujan, played by Dev Patel.
G. H. Hardy, played by Jeremy Irons.
Littlewood, played by Toby Jones.
Janaki, played by Devika Bhise.
Sir Francis Spring, played by Stephen Fry.
Major MacMahon, played by Kevin McNally.
The Man Who Knew Infinity is a 2015 British biographical drama film about the Indian mathematician
Srinivasa Ramanujan, based on the 1991 book of the same name by Robert Kanigel.
The film stars Dev Patel as Srinivasa Ramanujan, a real-life mathematician who, after growing up poor in Madras, India, earns admittance to Cambridge University
during World War I, where he becomes a pioneer in mathematical theories with the guidance of English mathematician and fellow collaborator, G.
Hardy, portrayed by Jeremy Irons.
Filming began in August 2014 at Trinity College,
Cambridge after eight years in development.
The film had its world premiere as a gala presentation at the 2015 Toronto International Film
Festival, and was selected as the opening gala of the 2015 Zurich Film Festival.
It also played other film festivals including Singapore International
Film Festival and Dubai International Film Festival.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, england,
mathematics, mathematician, mathematical theorem.
The tone is emotional.